export default [
  {
    quiz: "Cutting Operations",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "1.	All except _____ is not a system used for tool designation ? ",
        answerA: "ASA ",
        answerB: "ANSI ",
        answerC: "ORS ",
        answerD: "AISO ",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },

      {
        question: "2.	_______ is not a type of rake pattern ",
        answerA: "Neutral rake ",
        answerB: "Negative rake",
        answerC: "Positive rake",
        answerD: "Zero rake",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "3.	Which rake pattern is required when cutting is done at high speeds?",
        answerA: "Neutral rake ",
        answerB: "Negative rake",
        answerC: "Positive rake",
        answerD: "Zero rake",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: "4.	The method of metal cutting are ? ",
        answerA:
          "Orthogonal and oblique cutting a)	Orthogonal and oblique cutting .",
        answerB: "Diagonal and horizontal cutting. ",
        answerC: "Vertical and horizontal cutting ",
        answerD: "All of the above",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question: "5.	______ is not a type of chip formation in metal cutting? ",
        answerA: "Continuous chips ",
        answerB: "Continuous chips with built up edge ",
        answerC: "Discontinuous chips ",
        answerD: "Discontinuous chips with built up edge.",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Lathe Machine Operations",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "1.	On the lathe, work piece is held on all of the above except ?",
        answerA: "Chuck",
        answerB: "Mandrel",
        answerC: "Between center",
        answerD: "Saddle",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question: "2. ______ is not a turning operation ?",
        answerA: "Rough",
        answerB: "Shoulder",
        answerC: "Taper",
        answerD: "Forming",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question:
          "3.	Operations performed on the lathe using special attachments are ?",
        answerA: "Parting-off and drilling ",
        answerB: "Boring and reaming ",
        answerC: "Grinding and milling ",
        answerD: "None of the listed",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "4.	The preferred option for holding an odd-shaped work piece in a center lathe is ?",
        answerA: "Live and dead centers ",
        answerB: "Three jaws chuck ",
        answerC: "Lathe dog ",
        answerD: "Four jaws chuck",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question:
          "5.	Which of the following chucks in the lathe machine is known as universal chuck?",
        answerA: "Magnetic chuck ",
        answerB: "Face plate",
        answerC: "Three jaws chuck ",
        answerD: "Four jaws chuck",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Grinding Operations",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "1.	All these are grinding operations except ?",
        answerA: "Taper grinding ",
        answerB: "Cylindrical grinding",
        answerC: "Threading grinding ",
        answerD: "Machine grinding",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question: "2.	______ is not a surface grinding machine type? ",
        answerA: "Longitudinal spindle and rotary table type ",
        answerB: "Horizontal spindle and rotary table type ",
        answerC: "Vertical spindle and reciprocating type ",
        answerD: "Horizontal spindle and reciprocating type",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "3.	Precision grinders are used to finish parts to very accurate dimensions. The main types are all except ?",
        answerA: "Tool and cutter grinding machine",
        answerB: "Internal grinding machine ",
        answerC: "Special grinding machine",
        answerD: "Hand grinding machine",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question: "4.	Grinding machines are of ?",

        answerA: "Rough and precision ",
        answerB: "Rough and flexible ",
        answerC: "Precision and cylindrical ",
        answerD: "Internal and surface",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "5.	Abrasives used for grinding and polishing operations should have the following properties except ?",
        answerA: "Brittleness ",
        answerB: "Hardness ",
        answerC: "Toughness ",
        answerD: "Resistance",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Drilling Operations",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "1.	______ is not a drilling operation ? ",
        answerA: "Grinding ",
        answerB: "Drilling  ",
        answerC: "Boring ",
        answerD: "Milling",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question: "2.	Drilling machine tools are all except ? ",
        answerA: "Taper shank core ",
        answerB: "Two-lip twist",
        answerC: "Deep hole ",
        answerD: "Flat spade ",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question: "3.	In a drilling operation, the metal is removed by ?",
        answerA: "Shearing ",
        answerB: "Extrusion ",
        answerC: "Shearing and extrusion ",
        answerD: "Shearing and Compression",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question: "4.	The cutting edges of the twist drill are known as ?",
        answerA: "Flanks ",
        answerB: "Wedges ",
        answerC: "Flutes ",
        answerD: "Lips",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question:
          "5.	The ______ drilling machine is commonly used to drill small sized holes ? ",
        answerA: "Sensitive ",
        answerB: "Portable ",
        answerC: "Upright ",
        answerD: "Deep hole",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    quiz: "Milling Operations",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "1. The cutting tool in a milling machine is mounted on ?",
        answerA: "Spindle  ",
        answerB: "Knee  ",
        answerC: "Column  ",
        answerD: "Arbour",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question: "2.	In a milling machine, the feed is provided by moving  ?",
        answerA: "A rotating cutter into a stationary work piece ",
        answerB: "A rotating cutter into  a reciprocating work piece ",
        answerC: "A reciprocating cutter into a stationary work ",
        answerD: "A work piece into a rotating cutter ",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question: "3.	Up milling is also called as ?",
        answerA: "End milling ",
        answerB: "Face milling ",
        answerC: "Climb milling ",
        answerD: "Conventional milling",
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        question: "5.	Which is the simplest type of milling machine ?",
        answerA: "Universal milling machine ",
        answerB: "Ominiversal milling machine ",
        answerC: "Face milling  ",
        answerD: "End milling ",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question: "5.	The percentage of manganese in white cast iron is ?",
        answerA: "0.10% to 0.40% ",
        answerB: "2% ",
        answerC: "3.5% ",
        answerD: "4% ",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
    ],
  },
];
